So let's go, we'll do a rewind
meditation of gratitude and dive
into two parts,
let's start counting
and think of some
or here we all The diamond on the mountain
was knocked out,
choose something juice or some
piece of bread or some rice
anything
[music]
Imagine what he or she looks like
now Imagine where they got this food
Maybe in some store
Imagine all these people who
work in this store that
puts all these products on the
shelves and worked all day
it delivered vegetables fruits farms these are
stores
I worked
did this job when he was a student in
college it's hard work
it reaped the harvest
[music]
disappeared
we already owe them
time our body and they have the right
to ours they
already have the right even to our body
for what we do with it
and the very thought of giving thanks
The thought that they already have the right to
my time
it also has a history
and this is the second meditation that I want you to
practice today
itself
about what other people have
Yes, where is it from the source juice
I will hear
I want you to mentally
track  Let the thoughts
that
brought you to this point in time
consider the possibility
that other people already have a right
to your time so that
they are already owed some of
our time if we
respect
that everyone has a right in this world
then all these people already have
where did this idea come from in the first place
who said that they have equals about you
Why am I hearing this now I have heard during
this time well
and I thought that
I want to listen to this course I want to
know more
and what are you thinking about
I thought what good I can do in
my life
where did this thought come to me I
think
that when I was in college I heard about
this
[music]
I thought about how to enter college
and what my mom and dad
said about how it would be
nice for me to study in college
No I remember that I thought
about history and about the whole world about how I
studied in school I remember these thoughts
about what I felt when I
went to first grade
especially about what went wrong at school
I remember how I felt you
feeling I remember that I was curious about what
books are such people something
I remember
I remember such first day
cradles
I remember the feeling of the blanket covering me, the warmth and
softness. I remember thinking about
how soft and pleasant it was.
I want
two meditations to be done. The first
is physical.
Just choose what you have already eaten or what you are wearing, or where
you
are,
and simply trace it back to these
people who produced the material
that transmitted knowledge about how to
build a house for 50 thousand.
This is very cool.
You know,
for me, this is early in the morning. For example,
all your thoughts that you had. Look. Take it back.
How far can you
go? If you work well, you can
even reach that point in just a couple of
months,
and then you can.
You can do
this, perhaps,
all this time.
[music]
When you are full of enough
energy, trace your thoughts and
try to go back as far as you can.
This is a very deep
meditation.
It really promotes the ability to
see emptiness.
What kind of
thought
can you have with gaps? You will have this.
I had an
idea like this. 10.
You can even rewind.
Find
this very
[music]
Be with us, guys.